<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">The staff I would be working with is about the same age as me.</statement>
     <statement id="2">The staff I would be working with shares the same faith / religion as me.</statement>
     <statement id="3">The staff I would be working with is female.</statement>
     <statement id="4">The staff I would be working with is the same sexual orientation as me.</statement>
     <statement id="5">The staff I would be working with earns about the same income as me (same income level)</statement>
     <statement id="6">The staff I would be working with used to be a domestic worker.</statement>
     <statement id="7">The staff I would be working with lives in the same community as me.</statement>
     <statement id="8">The staff I would be working with is from the same hometown as me.</statement>
     <statement id="9">The staff I would be working with has the same level of education as me.</statement>
     <statement id="10">The staff I would be working with has children.</statement>
     <statement id="11">The staff I would be working with has personal experience with mental health issues.</statement>
     <statement id="12">Other people about my age seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="13">Other people that share the same faith / religion as me seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="14">Other women seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="15">Other people seeking out services from this nonprofit are the same sexual orientation as me.</statement>
     <statement id="16">Other people seeking out services from this nonprofit earn about the same income as me.</statement>
     <statement id="17">Other domestic workers seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="18">Other people living in my community seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="19">Other people from my hometown (or home country) seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="20">Other people with a similar education as me seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="21">Other people with children seek out services from this nonprofit.</statement>
     <statement id="22">When I walk into the office, I feel safe.</statement>
     <statement id="23">I can visit the office without other people outside knowing my purpose.</statement>
     <statement id="24">I do not have to provide personal information to staff if I do not want to.</statement>
     <statement id="25">I can communicate with staff by telephone or internet (e.g., Zalo, Messenger, WhatsApp.)</statement>
     <statement id="26">I can communicate with staff face-to-face. </statement>
     <statement id="27">I can share personal information, thoughts, or concerns with staff without other people (staff or visitors) listening to our conversation.</statement>
     <statement id="28">The office (reception, meeting rooms) feels warm and welcoming.</statement>
     <statement id="29">The office is clean and tidy.</statement>
     <statement id="30">The office is peaceful (not too noisy).</statement>
     <statement id="31">The furniture and seating are comfortable.</statement>
     <statement id="32">The office is located in a safe environment.</statement>
     <statement id="33">The organization has a license to operate in Vietnam.</statement>
     <statement id="34">My family supports me seeking services from this organization.</statement>
     <statement id="35">My friends/peers support me seeking services from this organization.</statement>
     <statement id="36">The organization can provide examples of its impact.</statement>
     <statement id="37">The leader of this organization is a respected community member.</statement>
     <statement id="38">Staff have received mental health care education and training.</statement>
     <statement id="39">The staff have provided mental health care services for many years.</statement>
     <statement id="40">Staff understand my questions and concerns.</statement>
     <statement id="41">Staff show that they care about my health and well-being.</statement>
     <statement id="42">When I walk into the organization, I am welcomed by a staff person. </statement>
     <statement id="43">When talking with staff, I am treated with kindness and dignity.</statement>
     <statement id="44">Staff make time for my questions and concerns.</statement>
     <statement id="45">The process and criteria for accessing services from this nonprofit is clearly explained.</statement>
     <statement id="46">I do not have to wait a long time before meeting with a staff person.</statement>
     <statement id="47">Before providing personal information, staff share how they would use my information.  </statement>
     <statement id="48">This organization provides me with the same quality of service as everyone else.</statement>
     <statement id="49">I am given a choice of services and service deliver options (I can choose the timeline, staff person to work with, etc.).</statement>
   </statements>
